Guide to the Stanford University, Provost's Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Office of Management and Budget, Series 4
  - Facilities files, 1960-1981
    - 01-10 President's Office, 1971-1977 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - 01- 80 Geology, Human Biology, Undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - 01-120 Sociology I, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - 01-120 Sociology II, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - 01-120 Sociology, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - 01-120 Sociology Reconstruction I, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - 01-120 Sociology Reconstruction II, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - 01-120 Sociology Reconstruction III, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - 01-120 Sociology I, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - 01-120 Sociology II, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - 01-160 Political Science, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - 01-500 Memorial Church, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Quad 02 - general parking lot "J", 1960-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Quad 02-02-10 bookstore expansion, 1966-1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Quad 02-02-20 Center for Eduactional Research, 1973-1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Quad 02-02-50 Crown Quadrangle - Law School, 1972-circa 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Quad 02-02-210 Braun Music Facility, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Quad 02-02-210 Braun Music Facility, 1968-1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Quad 02-02-300 Tresidder Memorial Union, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Quad 02-02-500 Terman Engineering Laboratory, circa 1960-1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Quad 02-02-570 Mecanical Engineering Labs/Shops, 1965-1975 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Quad 02-02-570 High Temperature Gas Dynamics, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Quad 02-02-580 Student Service (Old Union), 1976 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Quad 02-02-580 Student Service (Old Union), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Quad 02-02-590 Building 590, 1962-1973 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Quad 02-02-590 Building 590, 1974-1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Quad 02-03-210 New Library, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Quad 02-03-210 New Library, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Quad 02-03-210 New Library, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Quad 02-03-210 New Library, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - 03-300 Education, 1971-1977 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - 03-300 Education, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - 03-300 Education, 1981 (Box 22)
    - 04-490 McCullough Building, 1972-1977 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - 07-40/50 East Medical Science Building, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - 07-40/50 East Medical Science Building, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - 07-60 Cancer Virus Building, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - 07-60 Outdoor Primate Facility, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - 07-300 Medical Center, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - 07-300 Medical Center, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - 12-700 Searsville Lake correspondence, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - 12-700 Jasper Ridge, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - 12-700 Jasper Ridge, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 1975)
    - 12-700 Jasper Ridge, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Ad Hoc Capital Facilities Committee, Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Air conditioning policy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Architects, Undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Auditoria & classroom study, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Auditorium use fees & use criteria, Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1971-1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Building responsibility, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Campaign for Stanford - building survey, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Campus furnishings, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Campus security lighting, Undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - CEFA, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - CEFA, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - CEFA resource allocations, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Child care, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Child care, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Child care, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Childcare report, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Child care - SNAP, Undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Classroom scheduling, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Classroom scheduling, 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Classroom utilization study, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Classroom utilization study #2, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Code - deferred maintenance, Undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Code - fire, Undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Code - related problems general, 1973-1977 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Code - OSHA, Undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Conference Center information, Undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Copy centers, Undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Debt & debt policy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Depreciation Recovery Plant Fund, Undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Electric meters, Undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Emergency power, Undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Emeriti facility space, Undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Energy conservation - I, Undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Encina Space Complex, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Energy conservation, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Facilities & Planning Office, 1972-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Facilities & Planning Office external staff meetings, Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Facilities Planning & Procedures Process Form I & II, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Facilities & Planning Office funds, Undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Facilities & Planning Office funding chart, Undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Facilities & Planning Office miscellaneous, Undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Facilities & Planning Office office record, Undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Facilities & Planning Office protocol, Undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Facilities & Planning Office small projects, Undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Faculty/staff housing campus housing eligibility, Undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Faculty/staff housing loan maximums, Undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Frat renovation procedure, Undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - V general fraternity information, Undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Furniture, Undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Government facility use restrictions, Undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - GPI - program, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - GPI - program Ed Shaw, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - GPI - program Ed Shaw, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - GPI - Lomita Drive/Mayfield, Undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - GPI - pro rata policy, Undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - HEFA I & II, Undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - HEFA III, Undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - HEGIS - Higher Education General Information Survey, Undated (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Higher Education Act HEA VI, Undated (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Historical building preservation, Undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Hoover O&M Operations and Maintenance, Undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Interdisciplinary village (surge space), Undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Land use study, Undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Lasuen/Mayfield Mall, Undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Medical Center Facilities Coordination Cmte., Undated (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Medical Center Space Committee, Undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Modular building (trailers), 1966-1972 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - National Humanities Institute, Undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Naming of buildings, Undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Pauling space, Undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Parking VIP permits, Undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Pay phone installations, Undated (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Performing Arts Center, Undated (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Plant - general, Undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Plant & related fund summaries II, Undated (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Plant & related fund summary I, Undated (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Provost monthly status reports, Undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - RehabiIitation program, Undated (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Roads on Campus, Undated (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Sangha Gardens, Undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Service operations, Undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Solar Energy Research Institute (SERI), Undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Space inventory, 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Space off - Campus, Undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Space utilization, Undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Stadium, Undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Family Statue, Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Shopping Center, Undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Student housing, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Student housing, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Student housing, 1960-1972 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Student lounges, Undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Subsistence gardens, Undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Summer work load, Undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - The trees, Undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Time schedule maps, Undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - University bulletins, Undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - University Committee on Land and Building Development (UCLBD), 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - UCLBD - University Committee on Land and Building Development, 1960-1973 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Land and buildings, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - 07-300 Medical Center Clinical Pharmacology expansion, 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - 07-300 Medical Center Clinical Pharmacology expansion, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - 07-400 Falconer Library Biological Sciences, 1968-1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 07-400/410 Herrin Labs & Hall, 1978-1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - 07-400/410 Herrin Labs & Hall, 1967-1977 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - 07-940T Drug Interactin temp. bldg. (SUMC ), 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - 07-970T Koko's House, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - 08 Encina Pools, 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - 08-10 Encina Gym, 1977-1983 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - 08-10 Encina Gym, 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - 08-100 Athletics & PE, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - 08-300 Memorial Hall, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - 08-320 Tanner Fountain, Undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - 08-350 GSB, 1961-1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - 08-350 GSB Library expansion (Jackson Library), 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - 08-350 GSB, 1972-1977 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - 08-400 Old Steam Plant (band quarters), 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - 08-500 Galvez House (200 Galvez), 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - 08-600 Frost (Laurence) Amphitheatre, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - 09-100 Plant service building, Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - 09-110 Stores - 330 Bonair Siding, Undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - 09-120 Credit Union, Stanford Federal, Undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - 09-190 Telecommunications Center, Undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - 09-200 Fire and Police Facility, Undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - 09-300 Maples (Roscoe) Pavilion, Undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - 09-400 Commissary/Food Services (Residence Halls), Undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - 09-920T CCCS - Little Kid's Place, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - 10 - General Escondido village - general, Undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - 10-310 Tower House 860 Escondido Road, Undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - 10-145 Escondido V Highrise Mirrielees, Undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - 10-700 Cowell Student Health Center, Undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - 04-930T (Boys Town), 1975-1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - 04-930T (Boys Town), 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - 05 Felt Lake (general), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - 05-10 Lagunita Court, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - 05-100 Roble Hall, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - 05-200 Florence Moore Hall, 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - 05-300 Knoll, 1963-1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - 05-800 Golf driving range, 1967-1976 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - 05 New student residences (program), 1979 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - 05 New student residences II, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - 05 New student residences (Committee on Student Residences Architectural Consultants - all brochures), 1979 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - 06-10/20/30 Encina Hall, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - 06-10/20/30 Encina Hall, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - 06-10/20/30 Enicna Hall, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - 06-50 Eating clubs, 1964-1976 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - 06-200 Toyon Hall, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - 06-300/350 Crothers & Crothers Memorial Halls, 1967-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - 06-400 Wilbur Hall, Undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - 06-500 Stern Hall, 1965-1976 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - 06-600/650 Manzanita Park & Laundry Building, 1969-1975 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - 06-910T/920T Office of Development, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - 07 Medical School parking, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - 07 Medical Center Animal Facilities, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - 07-10/20/30 East Medical Science Bldg. (medical microbiology), 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - 07-100 Museum South Rotunda, 1973-1978 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - 07-100 Museum, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - 07-100 Dudley Hermarium, 1963-1975 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - 07-210 Seeley G. Mudd Chemistry, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - 07-250 Organic Chemistry, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - 07-270 Stauffer II, Physical Chemistry, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - 07-290 Stauffer III, Chemical Engineering, 1962-1972 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - 07-300 Medical Center, Cardiology/Radiology expansion, 1974-circa 1979 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - 03-210 New library, 1975 Sep-Dec (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - 03-210 New library, 1975 May-Aug (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - 03-210 New library, 1975 Jan-Apr (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - 03-210 New library, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - 03-400 Meyer Library, 1974-1977 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - 03-400 Meyer Library, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - 04-10 Sequoia Hall, 1970-1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - 04-50 Ventura Hall, 1963-1976 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - 04-150 Serra House, 1969-1977 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - 04-490 McCullough Bldg. fume hoods, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - 04-500 Albers Wall, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - 04-500 Albers Wall, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - 04-500 Albers Wall, 1971-1976 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - 04-500 Physics Lecture Hall, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - 04-540 Durand Building, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - 04-560 Mitchell Building Earth Sciences, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - 04-560 Mitchell Building mechanical systems, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - 04-700 Terman Engineering Center, 1969-1972 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - 04-700 Terman Engineering Library, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - 04-920T Dendral Modular Building, 1971-1974 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - 04-490 McCullough fume hoods, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - 04-200 Ginzton Laboratories, 1967-1976 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - 04-300 Electronics Research Lab, 1963-1976 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - 04-350 Applied Electronics Lab, 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - 04-400 Salvatori Geophysics Lab, 1966-1976 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - 04-450 Petroleum Engineering/Lloyd Noble Building, 1973-circa 1976 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - 01-120 Interim relocation, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 01-170 History Department, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 01-310 Architecture, 1963-1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - 01-420 Jordan Hall (formerly Biology), 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - 02-General parking lot "J", 1970-1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - 02-600 Clubhouse, 1963-1973 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - 02-610 Mechanical Engineering, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - 02-620 Old Firehouse, 1966-1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - 02-630 Stanford University Press, 1967-1977 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - 02-630 Stanford University Press II, 1967-1977 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 02-650 Storke Student Publications Building, 1960-1976 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - 02-670 Butler Building (mailing services), 1963-1968 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - 02-908 Drell Residence, 570 Alvarado, 1960-1973 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - 02-914 Delta Pusilon, 553 Mayfield, 1967-1973 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - 02-915 Rogers House, 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - 02-916 Mariposa House (Sociology), 1964-1976 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - 02-917 Owen House - Cal. Law Review Commission, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - 02-918 The Bridge, 640 Campus, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - 02-919 Campus Bike Shop, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - 02-925 Columbae House, 549 Lasuen, 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - 02-926 Beta Theta Pi, 557 Lasuen, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - 03-1 Stanford Art Gallery, 1964-1975 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - 03-1 Dohrmann Memorial Garden, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - 03-10 Cummings Art Building, 1971-1976 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - 03-50 Career Planning & Placement Center, 1960-1976 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - 03-55 Clock Bell Tower, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - 03-100 Hoover Tower, 1968-1976 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - 03-100 Hoover Tower, 1963-1967 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - 03-210/200 Green Library budget, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - 03-210 New library, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - 03-210 New library, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - 03-210 New library, 1976 May-Dec (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - 03-210 New library, 1976 Jan-Apr (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - 11-110 Bolivar House-582 Alvarado (Latin American), Undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 11-130 Huston House-575 Salvtra (Psych. Service), Undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 11-160 Hurlburt House-650 Mayfield Avenue, Undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 11-200 Grove II (Mayfield) -584 Mayfield, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 11-250 Gardiner Apartments - 624 Mayfield, Undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - 11-300 Delta Tau Delta-650 San Juan, Undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - 11-400 Ryan Laboratory, Undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - 12-10 Golf Clubhouse, Undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - 12-70 Student Observatory I, Undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - 12-160 Alpine House, Undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - 12-200 Ctr. Adv. Study Behavioral Sciences, Undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - 12-700 Jasper Ridge, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - 12-700 Jasper Ridge, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - 13-100 Hoover Pavilion (SUMC), Undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - 14-100 Central Steam & Chilled Water Plant, Undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - 14-110 Cedar Hall, Undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - 14-120 Cypress Hall, Undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - 14-130 Spruce Hall, Undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - 14-160 Jordan Quad, Undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - 14-170 Pine Hall, Undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - 14-200 Stanford Computer Facility funding, Undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - 14-200 George Forsythe Hall, 1977 Jan-Jul (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - 14-610 Art Studios - Searsville Warehouse, Undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - 14-700 Carnegie Institution-290 Panama St., Undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - 90- VII Pi Meson Medical Center, Undated (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - 90- Searsville Lake, Undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - 90- Searsville Lake leasehold, Undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - 90- SLAC Recirculating Linear Accelerator, Undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - 90- SLAC/PEP project, Undated (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - 90- SLAC synchrotron, Undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - 90- Webb Ranch, Undated (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station master plan, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - 90-100 Hopkins Marine Station Hovden Cannery, Undated (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - 90-110 Hopkins Marine Station Loeb Laboratory, Undated (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - 90-130 Hopkins Marine Station Agassiz Laboratory, Undated (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - 90-140 Hopkins Marine Station Monterey Boat Works, Undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - 90-925 VII-Welch Road & Medical Development Office, Undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Academic Planning Office Report, 1970-1980 (Box 31)
      Contains seperate reports for 1970-1971, 1971-1972, etc. through 1979-1980.
    - A Functional Description, Stanford Student Data Base System, 1976 (Box 31)
    - Budget Adjustment Program (BAP II ) - Final recommendations of income adjustments and budget reductions in the 1971-1972 Operating Budget, Undated (Box 31)
    - Stanford University Medical Center, Long Range Plan, Academic and Clinical Service, 1973 Oct (Box 32)
    - Stanford University Medical Center, Long Range Plan, facilities, 1973 Oct (Box 32)
    - Stanford University Medical Center, Long Range Plan, financial, 1974 Jun (Box 32)
    - The University and the Medical School; A View of the ReIatlonship at Stanford. William H. Northway, Jr., M.D., Undated (Box 32)
    - Quad 1, 1960-1983
      - 01 General, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - 01 General Duena Gate/Main Quad Gate, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - 01-01 Administration, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - 01-01 Humanities and Sciences, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - 01-01 Undergraduate Studies, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - 01-10 President's Office, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - 01-20 Classics, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - 01-30 Afro-American Studies-Compar. Lot., 1979- (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - 01-40 English, 1979- [1964-1972] (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - 01-50 English, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - 01-60 Humanities Special Programs, 1974- (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - 01-70 Religious Studies, 1968- (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - 01-90 Philosophy, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - 01-100 Anthropology-Linguistics, 1977- (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - 01-100 Anthropology, 1976- (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - 01-120 III Sociology-Recon., 1979- (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - 01-160 Political Science, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - 01-200 History Corner, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - 01-240 German Studies, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - 01-260 Language Corner, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - 01-300 University Council, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 22)
        - 01-260 Engineering Corner, 1960-1976 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - 01-310 Building 310, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - 01-320 Geology Corner, 1977- (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - 01-370 Physical Sciences, 1977- (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - 01-380 Sloan Mathematics Center (Math Corner), 1979- (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - 01-380 Sloan Mathematics Center (air-cond.), 1969- (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - 01-380 Computer Sci./Math. Sciences Statistics renovation, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - 01-420 Jordan Hall (Psychology), 1978- (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - 01-460 Margaret Jacks Hall, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - 01-460 Margaret Jacks Hall, 1978- (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - 01-500 Memorial Church organ, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - 01-500 Memorial Church organ, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - 01-500 Memorial Church, 1979- (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Quad 2, 1966-1983
      - 02-10 Bookstore, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - 02-23 Center for Educational Research (CERAS), 1979 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - 02-50 Crown Law Quad, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - 02-50 Crown Quadrangle Law School fountain, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - 02-60 Kresge Auditorium, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - 02-100 Bowman Alumni House, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - 02-120 Black House--418 Santa Teresa, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - 02-130 Harmony House--561 Lomita Drive, 1966- (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - 02-200 Music (including Dinkelspiel), 1978- (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - 02- 200 New music folder, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - 02-210 Braun (in design), 1979 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - 02-210 Braun (in design), 1978 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - 02-250 Institute for Energy Studies, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - 02-250 PBX Telephone Building, 1968- (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - 02-300 Tresidder Memorial Union, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - 02-350 Faculty Club, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - 02-400 Bechtel International Center, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - 02-500 Terman Engineering Laboratory, 1978- (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - 02-520 Mechanical Engineering, 1979- (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - 02-530 Civil Engineering, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - 02-540 Civil Engineering, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 21)